<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Economic Times Stocks RSS Feed</title><link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/markets/stocks/news</link><description>RSS feed generated from Economic Times Stocks news.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:01:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Nvidia's rally takes a break after forecasts leave investors nonplussed</title><link>/markets/stocks/news/nvidias-rally-takes-a-break-after-forecasts-leave-investors-nonplussed/articleshow/112902952.cms</link><description>The stock had fallen more than 5% before the bell after Nvidia on Wednesday forecast third-quarter gross margins that could miss market estimates and revenue that was largely in line.</description><guid>/markets/stocks/news/nvidias-rally-takes-a-break-after-forecasts-leave-investors-nonplussed/articleshow/112902952.cms</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:01:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ahead of Market: 10 things that will decide stock action on Friday</title><link>/markets/stocks/news/ahead-of-market-10-things-that-will-decide-stock-action-on-friday/articleshow/112902673.cms</link><description>India's benchmark indices Sensex and Nifty50 hit new record highs, driven by gains in financial and IT stocks, and Reliance Industries' plans to accelerate AI adoption and issue bonus shares. Analysts expect Nifty to continue its upward momentum towards 25,250, with crucial support at 25,000.</description><guid>/markets/stocks/news/ahead-of-market-10-things-that-will-decide-stock-action-on-friday/articleshow/112902673.cms</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:01:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Market Trading Guide: PFC, IndusInd Bank among 5 stock recommendations for Friday</title><link>/markets/stocks/news/market-trading-guide-pfc-indusind-bank-among-5-stock-recommendations-for-friday/slideshow/112902460.cms</link><description>Indian benchmark equity indices closed at fresh record highs on Thursday, led by RIL, financial and IT stocks. The S&amp;P BSE Sensex closed 0.43% higher at 82,134, while the NSE Nifty50 ended above the 25,150 mark."The short-term uptrend of Nifty continues to be positive. The next upside levels to be watched around 25360-25400 (1.382% Fibonacci extension). Immediate supports to be watched at 25000 levels," said Nagaraj Shetti, Senior Technical Research Analyst at HDFC Securities.Here are 5 stock recommendations for Friday:</description><guid>/markets/stocks/news/market-trading-guide-pfc-indusind-bank-among-5-stock-recommendations-for-friday/slideshow/112902460.cms</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:01:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian government gets Rs 5,091 crore dividend from IOC</title><link>/markets/stocks/news/indian-government-gets-rs-5091-crore-dividend-from-ioc/articleshow/112902100.cms</link><description>The government has received about Rs 5,091 crore from Indian Oil Corp as dividend, the Department of Investment and Public Asset Management (DIPAM) said on Thursday.</description><guid>/markets/stocks/news/indian-government-gets-rs-5091-crore-dividend-from-ioc/articleshow/112902100.cms</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:01:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NHPC gets shareholders nod to hike borrowing limit to Rs 50,000 cr</title><link>/markets/stocks/news/nhpc-gets-shareholders-nod-to-hike-borrowing-limit-to-rs-50000-cr/articleshow/112902044.cms</link><description>State-owned NHPC has received shareholders nod to raise its borrowing limit to Rs 50,000 crore in its annual general meeting held on Wednesday.</description><guid>/markets/stocks/news/nhpc-gets-shareholders-nod-to-hike-borrowing-limit-to-rs-50000-cr/articleshow/112902044.cms</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:01:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sebi proposes mandatory maintenance of communication record for 8 yrs</title><link>/markets/stocks/news/sebi-proposes-mandatory-maintenance-of-communication-record-for-8-yrs/articleshow/112901651.cms</link><description>Markets regulator Sebi on Thursday proposed to make it mandatory for all entities regulated by it to maintain communication records, including acknowledgements, for at least eight years.</description><guid>/markets/stocks/news/sebi-proposes-mandatory-maintenance-of-communication-record-for-8-yrs/articleshow/112901651.cms</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:01:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sebi proposes mandatory UPI block mechanism facility for secondary mkt trading</title><link>/markets/stocks/news/sebi-proposes-mandatory-upi-block-mechanism-facility-for-secondary-mkt-trading/articleshow/112901366.cms</link><description>Capital markets regulator Sebi has proposed mandating Qualified Stock Brokers (QSBs) to offer the facility of trading in the secondary market using the UPI-based block mechanism to their clients, similar to the ASBA facility.</description><guid>/markets/stocks/news/sebi-proposes-mandatory-upi-block-mechanism-facility-for-secondary-mkt-trading/articleshow/112901366.cms</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:01:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sebi mulls proposals on public interest directors' appointment process at market infra institutions</title><link>/markets/stocks/news/sebi-mulls-proposals-on-public-interest-directors-appointment-process-at-market-infra-institutions/articleshow/112901148.cms</link><description>Sebi on Thursday came out with proposals connected with the process adopted by the markets regulator for the appointment of public interest directors (PIDs) on stock exchanges, clearing corporations and depositories, in a move aimed at improving shareholders' participation in the process.</description><guid>/markets/stocks/news/sebi-mulls-proposals-on-public-interest-directors-appointment-process-at-market-infra-institutions/articleshow/112901148.cms</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:01:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US stocks open higher after Nvidia results, economic data</title><link>/markets/stocks/news/us-stocks-open-higher-after-nvidia-results-economic-data/articleshow/112900993.cms</link><description>Wall Street's main indexes opened higher on Thursday following AI chip firm Nvidia's largely-in line forecast and as data showed the U.S. economy remained robust adding to expectations of a September interest rate cut.</description><guid>/markets/stocks/news/us-stocks-open-higher-after-nvidia-results-economic-data/articleshow/112900993.cms</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:01:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These 7 FMCG stocks hit a 52-week high and rallied up to 45% in a month</title><link>/markets/stocks/news/these-7-fmcg-stocks-hit-a-52-week-high-and-rallied-up-to-45-in-a-month/slideshow/112900670.cms</link><description>On Thursday, India's benchmark index, the Sensex, surged by about 349 points, ending at 82,135. During this rise, 7 stocks in the BSE FMCG index hit their highest prices in the past year. Reaching a 52-week high is notable because it shows the highest value a stock has achieved in the last 12 months, providing valuable information for traders and investors. This milestone is essential for assessing a stock's current worth and predicting future price movements.</description><guid>/markets/stocks/news/these-7-fmcg-stocks-hit-a-52-week-high-and-rallied-up-to-45-in-a-month/slideshow/112900670.cms</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:01:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian government gets Rs 3,662 crore as dividend from LIC</title><link>/markets/stocks/news/indian-government-gets-rs-3662-crore-as-dividend-from-lic/articleshow/112900261.cms</link><description>Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) has paid the Indian government a dividend of Rs 3,662.17 crore, its largest shareholder. This payment follows a final dividend declaration of Rs 6 per share for FY 2023-24, totaling Rs 6,103.62 crore for the year.</description><guid>/markets/stocks/news/indian-government-gets-rs-3662-crore-as-dividend-from-lic/articleshow/112900261.cms</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:01:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>